

: 13th May 1993

: English, Hindi & Gujarati

: Single

: Indian

# JAY GOR

# Senior Executive

#### **PROFILE**

#### I'm Jay Gor.

I have been in the BPO industry for 7 years and have learnt that communication is the key to success here. BPO has taught me a lot about how and what to communicate with people. My most recent experience has been handling incoming chats and calls for Vodafone Ireland.

One reason I particularly enjoy this business is that it gives me the opportunity to connect with people. Using my strong analytical skills and logical thinking, build up a solid career in management by acquiring the vital theoretical and practical knowledge, Essential for business from a reputed institute. I always put my endeavours and all-out efforts to excel in every walk of my life. What I am looking for now is a challenging position where I can effectively contribute my skills and learn new ones, and ensure my growth through the organisation's growth.

#### SKILLS

**PERSONAL** 

Birthday

Relationship

Nationality

Languages

COMMUNICATION
CREATIVITY
TEAMWORK
ORGANIZATION
LEADERSHIP
TEAMPLAYER



#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

- Ambitious
- Positive thinker
- Adequate Communication Skills& Writing Skills
- Hard Working, Energetic & Well Disciplined
- Self-motivated and Flexible for any Shifts

## CONTACT



+91 - 99242 00556



jaygor444@hotmail.com



L/11 Lakeview Appt. Vastrapur, Ahmedabad -380015

#### **SOCIAL MEDIA**

**FACEBOOK**facebook.com/jay.gor.58

TWITTER
@Jaygor\_

INSTAGRAM @jaygor04

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelors of Business Administration (B.B.A)

Shri Chimanbhai Patel Institute of Business Administration

of Business Administration

2011 - 2014

Higher Secondary School (G.S.E.B)

A-One High School

2010 - 2011

Senior Secondary School (G.S.E.B)

H.B.Kapadia New High School

2008 - 2009

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Senior Executive**

June 2017 - Present

Vodafone Shared Services India | www.n.vodafone.ie

My role and responsibility is in chat process taking chats and guiding Irish customers with solutions of their query.

### **Admin Officer**

May 2016 - June 2017

Merit Plus BPO Pvt. Ltd. | www.meritplus.co.in

My role and responsibility was to clean and update CV's of doctors for U.K process as per requests.

#### Jr. Admin Executive

Feb 2015 - April 2016

Technomine BPO Pvt. Ltd. | www.technomine.biz

My role and responsibility was to input vacancies on online portal, to clean and update CV's as per requests and prepare contracts for Doctors.

## PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT AND PERSONAL INTEREST

- Completed Online course on Creative Innovation and Development
- Developing Innovative Ideas for New Companies
- Travelina
- Music
- Sports: Cricket, Volleyball and Badminton